You can now get MVR and PSP reports in the
same app with Spotter Sentinel.
Plus, you don't have to read and evaluate
each violation one by one.
Just upload the driver's license and run a
driver check. Spotter Sentinel
automatically
pulls the motor vehicle report and
pre-employment screening program documents
from
official
sources. Then, using advanced AI, Spotter
Sentinel reviews each violation, flags
roadside
inspections with issues and assigns a
final safety grade for the driver, saving
you
time
and ensuring accuracy. Transform your
safety management process.
Visit our website to get a free demo
today.